I thought I should tell you news like this in person.
こういう事は直接言った方がいいと思って
"News like this"?
こういう事って
It's about the anime adaptation...
アニメ化の話だが
Congratulations.
おめでとう
The Reversi anime will begin in October!
10月から「REVERSI」アニメ開始だ
yu
me
Dreams, dreams, dreams, dreams
ka
na
e
ru
ta
bi
ko
wa
re
te
yu
ku
me
As soon as I reach my goals, it all falls through again
na
ze
so
re
de
mo
ma
ta
So why do I run...
bo
ku
wa
sa
ga
su
ha
shi
ri
tsu
zu
ke
ru
...and search in spite of that?
hi
sa
shi
bu
ri
ni
de
atta
We met after such a long time
"
fu
n
i
ki
ka
watta?"
"Has the mood changed for us?"
tsu
ki
hi
wa
na
ga
re
ta
da
rou
So much time has passed
"
a
no
ko
ro
no
ho
u
ga
ta
no
shi
so
u
"
"It seemed like more fun back then"
ta
ku
sa
n
na
ku
shi
ta
We've lost so much
so
n
na
ko
to
wa
ki
zu
i
te
ru
n
da
I already know that, though
sa
ke
bi
tsu
zu
ke
ro
mo
ga
ki
tsu
zu
ke
ro
Don't stop screaming, don't stop struggling
da
re
no
ta
me
ni
na
n
ka
mou
i
da
rou?
You've done enough for others
ma
da
tsu
ta
e
i
ko
to
ga
a
ru
ma
da
I still, still have something I haven't told you yet
yu
me
no
sa
ki
ni
wa
yu
me
shi
ka
na
i
Beyond each of my dreams lies yet another dream
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神字幕组---
台本: 共由         翻译: 新人&poopy       繁化: 謙謙
校对：绫女       时间轴：Color
Correction and Declaration
An anime...
ア アニメ化
An anime!
アニメ化
I'm so glad! I'm so glad!
よかった よかったよ
Saikou?
サイコー
So a person can actually be this happy...
こんなうれしい事ってあるんだな
I'm so happy, it feels like my heart will stop.
幸せすぎて心臓止まりそうだ
What are you saying? You can't marry Miho if you're dead.
何言ってんの 死んじゃったら美保と結婚できないじゃん
Yeah.
そうだな
It starts now. Right from here.
これから これからだ
This really was your dream.
本当に夢だったんだな
There isn't an author out there who
wouldn't be happy about getting an anime,
アニメ化になって喜ばない作家はいないが
but you don't see many as happy as you.
ここまで喜ぶのは珍しい
Sorry, we got carried away.
すみません つい
Just celebrate today.
今日くらい浮かれてもいい だが
But...
Think carefully about the reason Reversi got an anime and Zombie Gun didn't.
なぜ「ZOMBIE☆GUN」ではなく「REVERSI」になったのか
その意味をよくかみしめるんだ
The reason?
意味
The Chief Editor chose Reversi for the future of Jack.
編集長は「ジャック」の未来のために「REVERSI」を選んだ
That's what I think.
僕はそう思う どういう事だか分かるな
You understand what that means, right?
He entrusted us...
僕たちに
with Jack's future?
「ジャック」の未来を
Yes.
そうだ 真の看板になれ
Become the true flagship!
Yes!
はい
Niizuma
Eiji Ltd
Hello?
はい
It's Heishi. Thanks for your work, as always.
お疲れさま 瓶子です
Thank you as well, Chief Editor.
編集長様 お疲れさまです
I think you've heard about it from Yuujirou.
雄二郎から聞いていると思うが
Yes.
はい
The anime that starts after CROW ends will be Reversi.
「CROW」のあとに始めるアニメは「REVERSI」に決定した
To tell the truth, Ashirogi isn't up to your level yet, Niizuma.
正直亜城木君はまだ新妻君には届いていない
However, I want them to one day become an
author that can stand shoulder to shoulder with you.
しかし亜城木君には新妻君に肩を並べる作家になってほしい
That is why I turned around and
chose Reversi to become an anime.
だからこそ あえて「REVERSI」をアニメ化する事にした
So that both of you can continue to compete with each other and grow.
君たちが互いにしのぎを削り 成長し続けていく
That is the future of Shounen Jack as I envision it.
それが私が思い描く未来の「少年ジャック」だ
I am sorry to have gotten your hopes up regarding this.
今回は期待させてしまい 申し訳ない事をした
What are you talking about, Chief Editor?
何を言ってるんです 編集長
This is the best!
最高なんですけど
I'm way more hyped up this way!
そっちの方が断然燃えます
I'll draw like I've never drawn before!
より燃えてこれから描けます
We did it.
やったな
I still feel like I'm dreaming.
まだ 夢見てるみたいだ
You have to tell Azuki that we got an anime.
亜豆にもアニメ化決まった事報告しないとな
Yeah.
As well as the fact that the heroine's role will be decided through an audition.
ヒロインはオーディションで決まるって事も
Of course, as the author, they will listen to your opinion,
もちろん作者である君たちの意見も聞き
and if you insist, they will give it due consideration.
僕たちが働きかければそれなりの配慮はしてくれる
However, the final decision will come from the director and the production company.
しかし 最終的に決めるのは制作側や監督だ
Azuki will be fine. She's got the popularity and the skills.
亜豆なら 人気実力共に大丈夫だ
We've gotten this far already. We have to fulfill the rest of your and Azuki's dream.
やっとここまで来たんだ 亜豆との夢もここでかなえないとな
Yeah.
We'll definitely fulfill it!
きっとかなう
New mail
We did it!
An anime adaptation
of "REVERSI" has been
approved to start airing in
October. Voice actors will
be decided through auditions.
Mashiro Moritaka
No subject
Congra
Azuki Miho
Incoming call
She's calling instead of texting me?!
メールじゃなくて電話
H-Hello?
は はい
Congratulations!
おめでとう
Thanks.
ありがとう
Just "congratulations," though?
でも「おめでとう」はちょっとひと事みたいじゃ
Satoru, you've changed.
「サトル変わった」
You used to be more kind.
「前はもっと人に優しかった」
Those are Naho's lines from Reversi!
「REVERSI」の菜保の台詞
You just went along with it? What do you mean?
You just
went along
with it?
What
do you
mean?
「合わせていた どういう意味」
You too...
Naho...
If everyone thought and acted the same as I... as Satoru does,
「みんなも私とサトルと同じように考え 行動すれば」
the world would be a much better place.
「すばらしい世界になる」
It's not too late. We can still remake it.
「まだ 間に合う やり直せる」
"Normalcy" and "common sense"
「普通とか常識とか そんなのは今世界を動かしてる人の押しつけ」
are just shackles imposed by the people who run the world.
Wow. That really is my ideal voice for Naho.
すごい やっぱり理想の菜保の声だ 完璧
It's perfect.
I have no other opinions or advice to give to you.
何の意見もアドバイスもないくらい
I didn't perform that to get your advice.
アドバイスが欲しくて演じたんじゃない
I just wanted to let you know that I'm also working towards our dream.
私も2人の夢に向かって努力してますって伝えたくなって
I can see that now.
うん 伝わってきた
I've also memorized most of her lines from Volume 2.
2巻収録分の台詞もほとんど暗記してます
Great!
すご
Want to hear them?
聞く
Sure.
うん
Oh, you're here.
来たか お疲れ
Good morning.
You, too.
お疲れさまです
There are two new offers for you that came in.
また君にやってほしいという話が2本来てる
The role of Shouko in Diploma Girl Shouko
「賞状少女翔子」の翔子役
and the role of Kamasu in A Child Star's Coming of Age.
「子役の成人式」のカマス役 こっちは男の子のキャラクターだな
Oh, that last one's a male character, though.
I won't do either.
どちらもやりません
Oh, okay. Either is fine—
うん そうか どちらも
What?!
ま まあ あんまり出過ぎるのも何だしな
Well, I guess becoming too well-known can be a bad thing.
If possible, I'd like to hold off
from any new work until summer.
できれば 夏まではもう仕事を増やしたくないんです
I don't get her. I don't get this girl.
分からん この子は分からん
But she's succeeding as a voice actress, despite her headstrong personality.
しかし 我を通しながらも声優として成功してるのも確か
All right. I won't put you in for any new work until summer.
分かったよ 夏までは仕事を入れない方向だな
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
Oh, and boss...
社長
Thank you for everything, as always.
いつもありがとうございます 感謝してます
I'm really thankful.
What? The role of Naho will be auditioned?
菜保役オーディションなの
Yeah.
I know Miho will definitely pass, but...
美保なら絶対受かると思うけど
Of course she will.
当たり前だろ 亜豆なら実力で役を取れるって
Azuki can get the role with just her skill alone.
I'll say.
うん そうだね
Sokkai High School       Female Student
Kitami      Ririka
Oh. Kitami Ririka is in Impromptu 12, too.
北見リリカって「即席12」にも出てたんだ
She's Katou's friend, right?
加藤さんの友達だよね じゃあ美保とも知り合いって事
Do you think she knows Miho, too?
She's a fledgling voice actress, after all.
声優の卵って言ってたよな
Oh, here it is.
あった あった 北見リリカのブログ
Kitami Ririka's blog.
Why are you looking her up?
何調べてんのよ
I'm just curious.
何となく気になるじゃん
She was cute.
あの子かわいかったもんね
It was because one of my friends is
an assistant to Ashirogi Mutou, who are serializing Reversi
and I made her ask them if I could come ^_^;
It turns out that Ashirogi are a duo
I wonder if it's okay for
me to say this?)
She wrote a post about the party the other day.
この間のパーティーの事が書いてある
"They're both really hot, kyaa!"
「お二人ともイケメン キャーッ」
"Unfortunately, one of them is married."
「が 残念ながら お一人は既婚」
She's talking about you, isn't she?
これって 秋人さんの事よね
Yeah.
"The other one happens to be dating a voice actress whom I admire."
「もう一人はなんとリリカの尊敬する声優さんと交際中とか」
"But I won't tell you who!"
「誰かは内緒だ」って
She didn't mention names, but this isn't good, right?
名前は伏せてあるけどマズいよな
Y-Yeah.
I'll call Katou and have her tell her friend to delete this post!
加藤さんに電話してこのブログすぐに削除してもらうように言う
I'm very sorry!
本当にごめんなさい
Well, she did delete it right away.
いえ すぐに消してくれたみたいだし
I told her never to let this happen again.
もうこんな事のないようによく注意しておきましたので
Well, the fact that Ashirogi is a two-man team,
いや 大体亜城木夢叶が2人組で
and that one of us is married
while the other is dating someone
片方が結婚してて 片方に恋人がいるなんて
isn't really of interest to most people.
一般の人から見たらどうでもいい事だもんな
But it'd be bad if it got out that the girl
you're dating is the voice actress, Azuki Miho.
その恋人が声優の亜豆美保ってバレたらマズいだろ
Her fans may get a nasty shock,
ファンの人がショック受けるかもしれないし
and when it gets out that we want her to play the role of the heroine in Reversi,
「REVERSI」のヒロイン演じてもらおうと思ってるのに
a work which was co-created by her boyfriend,
「原作者が恋人」って広まったら
they might accuse us of favoritism.
コネとかいろいろ言われる可能性だってあるだろ
R-Really?
そ そうか
There are some wild rumors on the 'net. You guys okay?
ネットですげぇ噂になってるけど大丈夫か
Huh? Rumors?
噂
That you and Azuki Miho are an item.
真城君と亜豆美保がデキてるって
Looks like there's someone who read Kitami Ririka's blog
北見リリカって声優のブログ見てネットに書き込んだやつがいるらしい
and posted about it on the internet.
Sounds like some classmate you had in middle school.
中学の同級生っぽいな
Uh, but...
I thought we were fine because we had her delete that entry two days ago!
でも それは2日前にブログ消してもらって
Ririka said in an interview that Azuki is a voice actress that she respects.
Anonymous
Azukyun also acted in the drama CD for PCP
Isn't the "A" in Ashirogi the "A" in "Azuki"?
もう大丈夫だと
Anonymous
I heard Ashirogi and Azuki Miho were
classmates in middle school.
The internet sure is scary.
怖～な ネット
Anonymous
Well, there we go!
I'm sure you know this already, but you shouldn't pay them any attention.
分かってると思うけどさ こんなの気にする事ないからな
Yes, I know.
はい 分かってます それに僕たちは何も悪い事はしていません
And also, we didn't do anything wrong.
"We didn't do anything wrong..."
何も悪い事してない だな
That's for sure.
We're fine, but what about Azuki?
俺たちは平気だけど
亜豆 大丈夫かな
I'll be leaving, then.
お疲れさまでした
You have one more recording session today.
今日はもう一本収録があるから
Okay.
はい
I'm from Touzai Sports!
「東西スポーツ」の者ですが
Is the "A" in Azuki the "A" in Ashirogi?
亜城木の「亜」は亜豆の「亜」というのは本当ですか
If you're from the press, then please let us through first!
取材でしたらプロダクションを通してからにして下さい
Do you really have a boyfriend?
アズキュン恋人いるって本当なの
It's not true, right?
うそだよね
Mashiro!
真城先生 今日の「東西スポーツ」見ました
Did you see today's Touzai Sports?!
Huh?
Popular voice actress
Azuki
Miho has
a boyfriend!?
Azuki
Miho has
a boyfriend!?
Azukyun
Her purported
boyfriend is
Mashiro, the artist
of the popular
manga author
Ashirogi Mutou,
who are currently
serializing Reversi
in Weekly
Shounen Jack
Her purported
boyfriend is
Mashiro, the artist
of the popular
manga author
Ashirogi Mutou,
who are currently
serializing Reversi
in Weekly
Shounen Jack
Mixing business
and pleasure!?
Azuki Miho (Azuki Miho)
Born in Saitama Prefercture on
November 5th, 1993
Notable appearances:
Seibijuaru Jogakuin Koutoubu
What's this?
な 何だよ これ
Hello, this is Weekly Shounen Jack.
はい 「週刊少年ジャック」
Ashirogi did what? I have no knowledge of that.
I cannot comment on that.
その件に関してはお答えできません
Sorry.
すまんな
Don't sweat it.
It's been so noisy in here ever
since that news article came out.
いえ 新聞に出てからすごい騒ぎですね
Is Ashirogi okay?
亜城木君たち 大丈夫でしょうか
Anonymous
Now that I think about it, all heroines in Ashirogi's manga resemble Azuki Miho.
Is that why Azukyun is the heroine
in PCP's drama CD?
They resemble her because she's his girlfriend, duh.
Anonymous
He got her to act in the drama CD,
basically favoritism.
They're just going to town on us.
なんか言いたい放題だよな
Anonymous
Favoritism ain't good.
They're saying that we just gave her that role in the PCP drama CD.
「『PCP』のドラマCDにも彼女だから出した」って
Don't look at it any more.
もう見るなよ
But I can't just ignore it!
だって ほっとけないだろ
All you've genuinely done is work hard towards your dreams.
サイコーと亜豆は純粋に2人の夢のために努力してきたんだろ
Why do they have to talk about you both like you're trash?
その2人が何でこんな汚いやつみたいな言われ方されなきゃいけないんだよ
Thanks.
ありがとう
Your feelings are enough for me.
シュージンのその気持ちだけでうれしいよ
The anime staff will come here on February 9.
2月9日にはアニメのスタッフがここに来る
If they're aware of this uproar, they may keep Azuki from getting the role.
この騒ぎを見たら 亜豆のヒロイン起用を渋るかもしれない
Are you okay with rumors like these destroying your dreams?
いいのかよ こんな噂に夢を潰されて
Okay, manuscript looks good.
よし 原稿OK
Um, everything's going to be okay, right?
あの 大丈夫ですよね
What exactly?
何がだ
Azuki Miho getting the role of Naho.
菜保役を亜豆美保にやってもらう事
Oh, that.
その事か
You haven't done anything wrong. There's no cause to worry.
悪い事してるわけじゃない 気にする事はない
But, this issue has gotten bigger than I ever imagined...
しかし ここまで事が大きくなってしまうと
Prince Eight
Prince Enterprise
I apologize on our behalf for Kitami's inexcusable actions.
この度はうちの北見が申し訳ない事を
I'm really sorry.
本当にごめんなさい
Azuki Miho is at the height of her popularity!
亜豆美保は今が人気絶頂なんだ
Of all the times to do this—
こんな時によりによって
Boss!
社長
What? You never raise your voice.
何だね 珍しく大きな声出して
Please don't be so hard on Kitami.
北見さんをそんなに責めるのはやめて下さい
She didn't mean any harm.
悪気はなかったんですし
How can you tell?
何でそんな事分かる
We've worked together before, so I know.
一緒に仕事したので分かります
She always seemed very friendly towards me.
彼女が私にすごく好意的なのが伝わってきましたから
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
I never imagined this would cause such a problem.
私まさかこんなに迷惑掛けちゃうなんて思ってなくて
It's okay.
いいんです 彼と交際しているのは本当ですから
It's true that we're in a relationship.
If it ends up clashing with my job as a voice actress, that's too bad.
それで声優としてやっていけなくなるというなら しかたありません
It's my weakness.
私の力不足です
You can't! You mustn't acknowledge that you have a boyfriend!
いかんぞ 絶対に恋人と認めたりしないでくれよ
I know!
そうだ 今週のラジオ放送ではっきり交際を否定するんだ いいな
During this week's radio broadcast, you'll firmly deny that you're dating anyone!
Understood?
Thank you for coming all the way out here.
遠いとこ わざわざありがとうございます
We apologize that it's so cramped and messy in here.
狭くて汚い所ですけど すみません
No problem. It's not that different from an anime studio.
いや アニメの現場も大差ないですよ
I'm the producer, Konaka.
プロデューサーの小中です
I'm the director, Ehara.
監督をする江原です
And here we have the screenwriter
Oobayashi, who will be adapting the script,
シリーズ構成脚本をやってもらう大林さんと
and Tamiya, the character designer and art director.
キャラクターデザイン総作画監督の田宮さんです
I'm Oobayashi, nice to meet you.
大林です よろしく
I'm Tamiya, nice to meet you also.
田宮です よろしくお願いします
Thanks, same to you.
こちらこそ
Let's all work well together.
よろしくお願いします
Animation supervision and production
Animation Production Studio
Producer
Konaka Manabu
And so, we'll respect the original work
ですので 原作を尊重してできるだけ原作どおりにと考えています
and try to follow it as closely as possible.
Okay.
はい
We would appreciate that.
僕たちもそれが一番うれしいです
If you have any requests, please let us know.
先生たちの方から何かご要望があれば言って下さい
A-About the voice actors...
せ 声優なんですが
Saikou.
サイコー
I want Azuki Miho to play Naho.
菜保は亜豆美保さんに演じてほしいと思っています
Not to be rude, sir, but are you aware of the internet rumors about this?
先生 失礼ですがネットなどで噂になってる事はご存じですか
Yes.
はい 亜豆美保と僕は交際しています
Azuki Miho and I are in a relationship.
So they were true.
本当だったんですね
In that case, we must be careful about giving her that role.
だとすると 起用は慎重に考えた方がよさそうですね
Why?
何でですか 菜保のイメージにも合ってます
She fits the image of Naho.
And she's a top-class voice actress among her age group.
演技だって今の若手の声優の中ではトップクラスのはずです
Takagi.
高木君
Considering the current situation, we'd get accused of favoritism if she got the role.
今の状況ではコネで起用したと言われかねません
There are people who frown upon the idea of Mr. Mashiro and Ms. Azuki in a relationship.
真城先生と亜豆さんが交際している事を快く思わない人もいます
That might negatively affect the anime.
その事が作品にとってもマイナスになるかもしれません
We will decide the roles through
auditions, just as we originally planned.
声優は予定どおりオーディションで決めます
Of course, if you say you want us to consider Azuki Miho, we will.
もちろん 亜豆さんが受けたいと言えば受けてもらいます
But we will offer the role of Naho to the
candidate most suited to the character.
その上で菜保役にふさわしいと思った声優に演じてもらいます
Director, that wouldn't...
監督 そうは言っても
Well, I respect your feelings as well as the authors', but...
いえ 監督や原作者さんの気持ちは尊重したいとは思いますが
The director may have said so,
監督はああ言ってくれたけど プロデューサーがあそこまで反対だと
but if the producer is that against it, I wonder how this'll end up.
どうなるんだろうな
Who has more influence, anyway? The producer or the director?
てか プロデューサーと監督ってどっちが立場が上なんだろう
It'll be fine!
大丈夫 亜豆は必ず実力で役を取る
Azuki will definitely get the role through her acting skill.
There's no doubt about it!
取るに決まってる
Who are you trying to convince, Saikou?
サイコー ちょっと無理してね
You think there's no chance, don't you?
「やっちまった」と思ってね
No, I don't!
思ってない
The anime staff came
to our studio today.
I clearly told them that
you and I are in a relationship.
The director said  that the role would
still be decided through auditions.
Maybe I shouldn't have let
on that we were really dating?
The anime staff came to our studio today.
「今日はアニメスタッフが仕事場に来てくれました」
I clearly told them that you and I are in a relationship.
「スタッフには僕と亜豆さんが交際していることをはっきり伝えました」
The director said that the role would still be decided through auditions.
「その上で監督は菜保役はオーディションで決めると言ってくれました」
you and I are dating.
The director said  that the role would
still be decided through auditions.
Maybe I shouldn't have let
on that we were
really dating?
Maybe I shouldn't have let on that we're really dating?
「でも 付き合ってるってバラしたのまずかったかな」
Azuki Miho
No subject
My boss told me today to deny
that we're in a relationship on
this week's radio broadcast.
We're not seeing each other,
so it's close enough, he says.
My boss told me today to deny that we're in a relationship on this week's radio broadcast.
「私 今日社長に今度のラジオで交際してないって言うよう言われました」
We're not seeing each other, so it's close enough, he says.
「会ってないんだから それで通るって」
Mashiro Moritaka
No subject
Certainly, it doesn't look
like we're actually dating
so it's okay.
Certainly, it doesn't look like we're actually dating, so it's okay.
「確かにはたから見たら付き合ってるように見えないから 大丈夫」
But all I really want
is to shout out
"I love Mashiro Moritaka!"
But all I really want is to shout out "I love Mashiro Moritaka!"
「でも本当は私は真城最高くんを愛していますって大声で呼びたい」
Mashiro Moritaka
No subject
But for your sake,
you should do what
your boss said
and deny it.
For your sake, you should do what your boss said and deny it.
「社長の言う通りはっきり交際を否定した方がいいかもしれない」
「亜豆のためにも」
Ashirogi Mutou
Miho, can I come in?
美保 いい
Sure.
Are you okay?
大丈夫
Miho, you and Mashiro are both
chasing your dreams together, right?
美保たちは2人で夢を追いかけてたのね
I've told you this before, but I once
exchanged correspondence with a man,
前に話したと思うけど
お母さんが文通してた人とはそれだけで終わっちゃったの
but nothing came of it.
So—
だから
That man was Mashiro's uncle, Kawaguchi Tarou. Right?
その相手の人真城君の叔父さんの川口たろう先生でしょ
You knew?
知ってたの いつから
For how long?
Since our third year in high school.
高3の時に
Knowing that just made me want to be with Mashiro more.
知ったから 余計真城君と一緒になりたい
Maybe he feels the same way.
もしかしたら 真城君もそう思ってるかもしれない
Miho, I'm cheering you on.
美保 お母さんも応援する
I feel proud that my own daughter has such a wonderful romance.
自分の娘ながら こんなすてきな恋愛をしている事を誇りに思うもの
Three minutes before we air.
本番3分前
Listen up! You have to say "We're not dating!"
いいな「交際はしていない」
and "That was a false rumor started by a boy I went to middle school with!"
「中学の同級生というだけで勝手に立てられた噂」そう言うんだ
Okay?!
Boss, calm down!
社長 落ち着いて
If you can't put this rumor to rest, your life as a voice actress is over!
ここでうまく交際を否定できなければ 声優生命は終わりだぞ
You're exaggerating.
そんな大げさな アイドル声優として売りたいだけだろ
He just wants to sell her as a "perfect" voice actress.
You should do what your boss said and deny it.
「社長の言うとおりはっきり交際を否定した方がいいかもしれない」
For your own sake.
「亜豆さんのためにも」
What?
Deny that you're in a relationship?
交際を否定しろって
Yeah.
Her boss told her to say that on today's radio broadcast.
社長に「今日のラジオで言え」って
But denying it will make you both feel complicated about the whole thing.
でもさ つきあってないって言われるのも複雑な心境よね
That's how it has to be.
しかたないよ その方が亜豆のためになるなら
It's better for her this way.
Five seconds.
5秒前 4 3 2
Four, three, two...
Good evening.
こんばんは 亜豆美保です
This is Azuki Miho.
Everyone, do you have dreams?
皆さん 夢を持っていますか
Hey, at least follow the cues.
おい タイトルコールぐらいしろ
Those of you who are working towards a dream...
夢を持ち それに向かって頑張っている人
Those of you who are searching for one...
今 夢を探している人
I'm cheering you on.
What are you doing?  Deny it already!
私はその人たちを応援したい
何言ってんだ 早く交際を否定しろ
I am dating the manga author Mashiro Moritaka, the artist of the Ashirogi Mutou duo.
私はマンガ家亜城木夢叶
作画担当の真城最高さんと交際しています
早くCMに
Quickly, cut to a commercial!
But we just started!
今始まったばかりで
I love Mashiro Moritaka!
真城最高さんを愛しています
Before I became a voice actress
まだ私が声優デビューする前
Okay, keep going.
よし 気抜いところで このままいくぞ
and before he became a manga author,
彼がマンガ家としてデビューする前中学3年の時です
we made a promise in our third year of middle school.
約束しました いつか彼が描くマンガがアニメになり
That one day, the manga he drew would become an anime,
and that I'd play the lead female role in it.
そのヒロイン役を私がやる
And if that dream came true, we'd get married.
その夢がかなったら結婚する
That's the dream we've both held dear for so long.
それが彼と私がずっと持ち続けてきた夢です
Miho.
美保
Typical Azuki.
亜豆らしいな
It's been our dream since our third year of middle school.
中学3年の時からの夢です
Perhaps this isn't something I should have told my fans who have supported me,
もしかしたら私を応援してくれるファンの皆さんに
言うべき事ではなかったかもしれません
but I don't want to lie to my precious fans.
でも 私は大切なファンにうそを言う事が嫌です
I've decided to tell my fans the truth.
ファンの皆さんに本当の事を伝えようと決心しました
Okay, cut to commercial.
よし CMだ
Azukyun Night!
Yes... Yes...
はい あっ はい
Hey, don't screen each individual call at a time like this.
おい こんな時にかかってくる電話にいちいち取り合うな
A girl in tears is saying that she supports Azuki!
女の子が涙声で「私はアズキュンを応援する」って
People on the net are saying that they're touched—
ネットでも感動したっていう人が
Really?
本当か
Azuki?
亜豆さんCM明けリスナーの電話つないでいいか
After the break, can I put some
calls from the listeners through?
They say they're supporting you.
応援するって電話が来てるんだ
ちょっ 生放送でそんな事
Doing something like that on a live broadcast—
Please put them through.
つないで下さい
I want to properly face my fans.
ちゃんとファンの声と向き合いたい ここで逃げたくありません
I don't want to run from this.
Okay. We'll choose some calls to put through.
よし 分かった
つなぐ電話は選ぶ
We are receiving many calls from all of you.
皆さんから たくさん電話を頂いています
Today, I would like to talk to as many of you as I can.
今日はできるだけ多くの皆さんと直接お話したいと思います
Good evening. Your name and age?
こんばんは お名前とお年を
Tokumei Kibou, 22 years old.
匿名希望 22歳 会社員です
I work in an office.
I'm touched by what you said—Yeah, like hell I am!
アズキュンの今の話に感動してなんて言うかよ バカヤロー
Idiot!
Th-That's so mean.
ひ ひどい
Will Azuki be fine?
大丈夫か 亜豆
I'm sorry for hurting you.
傷つけてしまって ごめんなさい
But thank you for letting me know your true feelings.
でも 本当の気持ちを聞かせてくれて ありがとうございました
Just stop this already!
もう やめてくれ
She's shaking.
震えてる
She's shaking. Just look at her.
震えてるんですよ 彼女は
Even so, she's fighting all alone.
震えながらも たった1人で闘ってる
The next one's a girl who says she was really
moved by the story. I think this one will be okay.
次女の子だし 感動してるの伝わってくるので 大丈夫だと
Okay, put it through.
よし 回せ
I'm Sara, a 18 year old student.
サラ 18歳 学生です 交際宣言感動しました
I was so touched by your announcement that you're in a relationship.
Thank you.
ありがとう
Azukyun, you've been dating him since middle school, right?
アズキュン中学の時からずっと彼とつきあってるんですよね
Yes.
はい でも中学卒業してから会ったのは彼が入院してる時とあと2回くらいです
But since graduating from middle school,
I've only seen him when he was
hospitalized and two other times.
So, you haven't seen him at all other than that?
じゃあ あとは会ってないんですか
Right.
はい 電話も10回より少ないかも
And I've only called him about 10 times.
The rest of our correspondence consists only of text messages.
あとはメールでやり取りしてるだけです
Really?
ほんとに
That's because we decided we wouldn't meet until our dreams came true.
夢をかなえるまでは会わないって決めたんです
That's great!
すっご～い でも アズキュンのファンは男の子が多いから
But since your fans are mostly guys, aren't you
afraid that you're going to lose some fans over this?
今回の事でファンが減っちゃうんじゃない
Can we fit in one more?
もう一本 いけるか
Yes.
はい でもこの電話は
But this call is...
Azuki, this is the last call.
亜豆さん最後の電話だ
The next call will be the last.
次の電話で最後になります
I apologize to all the other callers I couldn't talk to.
電話してくれたのに話せなかった皆さん ごめんなさい
Good evening. Your name and age?
もしもし こんばんは
お名前とお年を
Mashiro Moritaka, manga author. 24 years old.
真城最高 マンガ家 24歳です
Mashiro?
真城君
If this is your real boyfriend, you should tell your listeners.
本当の彼氏だったら ちゃんとリスナーにそう言って
Everyone, this is the person I am dating, Mashiro Moritaka.
皆さん 先ほどお話した私の交際相手の真城最高さんです
I couldn't sit still after hearing all this.
聴いていたら 居ても立ってもいられなくなって
She's trying so hard.
彼女がこんなに頑張ってるんです
Please let me say something, too.
僕にもひと言言わせて下さい
Azuki Miho is a voice actress!
亜豆美保は声優です 彼女を彼女の声を信じてほしい
Please believe in her voice!
You should be able to tell if all her performances
今までの演技が皆さんを裏切るようなものだったのか
were lies or not!
考えてもらえば分かるはずです
I believe that Azuki Miho can get the role with her skills alone!
僕は亜豆美保は実力で役を勝ち取ってくれると信じています
That's all I wanted to say!
僕が言いたいのはそれだけです
Mashiro, I...
真城君
私 オーディション受かってみせます
will pass the audition.
do
u
shi
te
da
ro...
i
tsu
mo
so
u
sa
Why, I wonder?
chi
ka
zu
ku
ta
bi
ka
ra
ma
wa
ri
no
yu
me
Whenever I am close to fulfilling my goals, all effort becomes fruitless
ma
e
wo
mu
i
te
shi
ga
mi
tsu
i
te
sou
su
ko
shi
zu
tsu
We walk ahead, hold each other, and with little things
ya
ku
so
no
a
ba
sho
he
to
sa
e
ai
na
ga
ra
we support each other to reach what we promised
ji
shi
n
ga
ta
ri
na
i
to
ki
wa
mu
ne
ni
te
wo
a
te
When we lack confidence, we put a hand to our heart
bo
ku
ra
ga
tsu
zu
t
ta
pe
e
ji
yo
mi
ka
e
so
u
and reread the pages we assembled into a story
kyo
u
ma
de
so
shi
te
a
su
he
to
tsu
zu
i
te
yu
ku
no
sa
They lead up to today and continue into the morrow
ta
i
se
tsu
na
yu
me
ga
ka
na
u
so
no
hi
ma
de
We will always be ourselves
a
ri
no
ma
bo
ku
ra
de
zu
tto...
until the day that our dreams come true
Next Time
Preview
I hope Mashiro's girlfriend passes the audition!
真城先生の彼女オーディションに受かるといいですね
I know Azuki can do it.
亜豆ならきっとやってくれる
Next time: Mic and Script.
次回 マイクと台本
Mic and
Script
Love is more wonderful than dreams.
愛は夢よりもすばらしいです